cellbikes.com.au 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy

Bicycles Online is committed to providing you with a high level of customer service. This includes protecting and maintaining the privacy, accuracy and security of your personal information. We are bound by and will abide by the National Privacy Principles in the Privacy Act (Cth) 1988 . This is in addition to our existing obligations under the Privacy Act.

#### **What personal information do we collect and hold?**

In the process of conducting our business we are likely to collect a wide range of personal information about you. The type of personal information we collect always includes your name, residential and billing address, email address, telephone or mobile numbers and products and services we provide to you.

We don’t store any credit card information on our web site. We pass it onto our bank for processing.

#### **How do we collect personal information?**

Bicycles Online collects personal information directly from you when you submit it online at BicyclesOnline.com.au or when entered into our point of sale system at our store. There may be occasions when we collect information from publicly available sources or third parties. This information includes names, email addresses, telephone numbers and social media profile name sourced from permission based marketing activities.

#### **Cookies and Web beacons**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We use session ID cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited.

Some of our business partners (e.g. tracking utility company) use cookies and Web beacons on our site. We have no access to or control over these tracking technologies.

Bicycles Online advertises with Google. Google may show you our ads based on your having visited our site. If you do not wish to see these ads you can opt-out by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page here http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.

#### **Rate and Review**

If you provide a review or rating for a product available through Bicycles Online we reserve the right to publish part or all of your review or rating together with your first name and suburb.

#### **Links to Other Sites**

This Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Bicycles Online. Please be aware that we, Bicycles Online, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.

#### **How do we use personal information?**

In order to improve and better our offers and service, we may keep track of patterns of use in the e-mails and social interactions we send. By supplying us your information, you have given us permission to communicate to you via mail, e-mail, SMS, MMS, social media and telephone to inform you about services we deliver relevant to you indefinitely.

#### **Disclosure of personal information**

We may use or disclose your personal information to organisations outside Bicycles Online for purposes relating to the management of your account with us. Such organisations include: Service providers who manage the services provided to you; mailing systems which organise delivery of the products you have purchased; live help service providers, maintenance and repair services; market research; and our professional advisers, accountants, lawyers and auditors.

We require these organisations to adhere to strict confidentiality of your personal information and also seek to ensure that they adhere to the National Privacy Principles. These service providers may not use your personal information for their own marketing purposes.

#### **Security**

Bicycles Online take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is secure. We have robust systems and procedures in place to protect your privacy whenever we collect, store and use or disclose personal information. We are continually upgrading these systems and reviewing our procedures to ensure the highest standards of security are used to protect your personal information. As a condition of working at Bicycles Online all our employees sign a confidentiality agreement.

#### How to access and amend personal information

If you wish to obtain a copy of our data privacy policy, access the personal information we hold about you or your personal information is inaccurate, incomplete outdated or to unsubscribe, please direct any queries regarding your privacy rights email sales@bicyclesonline.com.au.

The release of information is subject to some exceptions such as information relating to existing or any anticipated legal proceedings, together with exceptions provided by the Privacy Act. Our objective is to respond to any request within a reasonable timeframe and no later than 30 days.

#### **How your information may be shared**

Except for the purposes outlined in the Bicycles Online Privacy Policy, we never sell or disclose your personal information. However, we may release personal information under the following circumstances:

  * when requested by the courts or laws (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency;

  * where we deem a company or an individual may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of; and/or to appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

#### **Changes in this Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this document, the home page and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.
